{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":null},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3218","name":"Midtown Shangri-La","address":"4710 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Cholada Chan","licenseNumber":"064628","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.06525,42.35403","geojson":{"id":"3218","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.065246859,42.354029295]},"properties":{"name":"Midtown Shangri-La","owner":"Cholada Chan","address":"4710 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"064628","establishmentid":"3218","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/30/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1596","name":"Cass Cafe","address":"4620 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"450","name":"Blimpies","address":"108 W Hancock","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5045","name":"Sweet Lorraine's Fabulous Mac n' Brewz","address":"4870 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4352","name":"Tim Hortons","address":"4830 Cass Ave, Suite A","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622777","name":"Tim Hortons","address":"4830 Cass Ave, Suite A","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4406","name":"Byblos Cafe & Grill II","address":"4830 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622646","name":"El Taco Veloz LLC","address":"4614 Second Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5345","name":"Juice Joint Detroit","address":"4614 Second Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"238","name":"Bronx Bar","address":"4476 Second Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1161","name":"Olympic Grill","address":"119 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43437","inspectionDate":"2018-09-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER DRY STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"41561","inspectionDate":"2018-02-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) The temperature of the wash solution in spray type warewashers that use hot water to SANITIZERS may not be less than:     \r\n(1) For a stationary rack, single temperature machine, 74°C (165°F);(Pf)   \r\n(2) For a stationary rack, dual temperature machine, 66°C (150°F); (Pf)   \r\n(3) For a single tank, conveyor, dual temperature machine, 71°C (160°F);(Pf) or\r\n(4) For a multitank, conveyor, multitemperature machine, 66°C (150°F).(Pf)  \r\n(B) The temperature of the wash solution in spray-type warewashers that use chemicals to SANITIZE may not be less than 49°C (120°F). (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine wash solution temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 120 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"}]},{"inspectionid":"39396","inspectionDate":"2017-07-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Next to the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"On top of the Cabinet (upper)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37591","inspectionDate":"2017-01-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3218"}}